Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education In Asia Records, Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- United Board Consolidated General File -- Addendum, 1959-69; Series II
  - Higdon - Hipps, 1958-66 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - Ho - Honey, 1959-61 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Hong, Suk-Ki - Hoover, G., 1953-60 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Hoover, Lyman, 1958-1968 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Horn, Francis H., 1958-63 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Horton, Mildred (Mrs. Douglas), 1958-64 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Horton, Walter M. - Howatt, 1958-59 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - Hsia - Hsieh, L., 1958-66 (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - Hsich, Pei-chih, 1959-63 (Box 14, Folder 170-171)
  - Hsiung - Hsu, F. K., 1959-64 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Hsu, Joan - Hsu, M., 1959-64 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Hsu, Serge Jih Chen, 1954-61 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Hsu - Huac, 1954-64 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Huang, Chen ya - Huang, M. C., 1955-58 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - Hudson, Roy - Hull, Alice M., Estate, 1958-61 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Hull - Hume, Dr. Mrs. Edward H. Memorial Fund, 1956-60 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Hung, Frederick, 1952-60 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Hunt, Chester, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Hunt, Frank R., 1957-62 (Box 14, Folder 180-181)
  - Hunt, Mrs. R. B., 1960 (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - Hunter, James Maude (see also: Tunghai, Series IV), 1956-61 (Box 15, Folder 182-184)
  - Hussey - Hwa Nan College, 1958-64 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Hwang - Idris, Muhammad, 1958-64 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Illick, J. Theron and Bernice, 1958-60 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - Imperial, George Bolyn - Indonesia, 1958-61 (Box 15, Folder 188)
  - Indonesian Christian University (Djakarta), 1956-64 (Box 15, Folder 189-190)
  - Indonesian Council of Churches - Indonesian Student Christian Movement, 1958-61 (Box 15, Folder 191)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs - Institute of International Education, 1958-60 (Box 15, Folder 192)
  - Interarea Program, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 193)
  - Interchurch Center, 1957-58 (Box 15, Folder 193-195)
  - I.B.M. Corporation, 1959-64 (Box 16, Folder 196)
  - International Christian University, Japan (see also: Japan International Christian Univ.), 1958-60 (Box 16, Folder 197)
  - International Foundation (until 1966 - China International Foundation), 1960-71 (Box 16, Folder 198)
  - Irving Trust Co. - Irwin, Mercedes, 1956-60 (Box 16, Folder 199)
  - Irwin, Richard G. - Jackson, W. E., 1958-60 (Box 16, Folder 200)
  - Japan International Christian University Foundation, 1961-64 (Box 16, Folder 201)
  - Japan International Christian University, Publicity Materials (see also: International Christian Univ., Japan), 1957-59 (Box 16, Folder 202)
  - Jenness, Lillian H. (Mrs. Richard), 1955-59 (Box 16, Folder 203)
  - Johnston, M. E. - ~Jones, D. C., 1958-61 (Box 16, Folder 204)
  - Jones, I. - Jones, James A., 1960-66 (Box 16, Folder 205)
  - Jones, John Price, Company: A Survey, Analysis and Plan for the U.B.C.H.E.A., 1958 Jul (Box 16, Folder 206)
  - Jones, John Price, Company: Correspondence, 1959-60 (Box 16, Folder 207)
  - Jones, Tracey K., Jr., 1958-64 (Box 16, Folder 208)
  - Judd, Walter - Junior Year Abroad Letter, 1960-65 (Box 16, Folder 209)
  - Kagawa, T. - Kalangie, M., 1958-60 (Box 17, Folder 210)
  - Kam, K. - Katada, D., 1954-61 (Box 17, Folder 211)
  - Kausch, D. - Kelly, C. R., 1958-60 (Box 17, Folder 212)
  - Kennelly, R. G. - Kepner, C. D., 1959-63 (Box 17, Folder 213)
  - Kilpatric~, W. H. - Kim, Myung Sun, 1959-60 (Box 17, Folder 214)
  - Kim, Soon Eung - Klingensmith, M. J., 1958-64 (Box 17, Folder 215)
  - Knabe - Knowles, 1960-62 (Box 17, Folder 216)
  - Ko, Niang Ho, 1957-62 (Box 17, Folder 217)
  - Kok - Korea, Miscellaneous, 1954-64 (Box 17, Folder 218)
  - Kung - Kwok, 1958-62 (Box 17, Folder 219)
  - Lai, David, 1958-60 (Box 17, Folder 220)
  - Lai, W. H. - Lamberton, M., 1959-67 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Land, Roy, 1959-64 (Box 17, Folder 222-223)
  - Landolt, George and Doris, 1956 Nov-1963 (Box 18, Folder 224-225)
  - Lane, O. M. - Lanier, E. A., 1958-61 (Box 18, Folder 226)
  - Larsen - Lau, 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 227)
  - Lauby, Paul T., 1968-70, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 228)
  - Lawney, Josephine, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 228)
  - Lawrence, Margaret, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 228)
  - Leavens, Marjorie (Mrs. Dickson H.), 1961-64 (Box 18, Folder 229)
  - Leber - Lee, Aaron, 1957-59 (Box 18, Folder 230)
  - Lee, Allan H., 1956-59 (Box 18, Folder 231)
  - Lee, Rose Marie, Fund, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 232)
  - Lee, Jerome, 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 232)
  - Lee, Joseph Yuen Chor, 1958-59 (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Lee, L. - Lee, P., 1962-66 (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Lee, R. - Lee, Y., 1959-65 (Box 18, Folder 234)
  - Lei - Leiper, H. M. W., 1958-60 (Box 18, Folder 235)
  - Lemnitzer, L. L., 1957-59 (Box 18, Folder 236)
  - Lenz - Leung, S. C., 1950, 1957-64 (Box 18, Folder 236)
  - Lewis and Clark College, 1958-61 (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Lewis, C. - Li, He, 1958-63 (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Li, Hung-chiang, 1962-64 (Box 18, Folder 238-239)
  - Li, Lewis - Li, Seung-Ping, 1961-65 (Box 19, Folder 240)
  - Li, Tsung-Han, 1959-60 (Box 19, Folder 241)
  - Librarians' Conference, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 241)
  - Lie - Lim, Mr. Mrs. Edward C., 1956-63 (Box 19, Folder 242)
  - Lin, Chao-te, 1957-61 (Box 19, Folder 243)
  - Lin, Che - Lin, T., 1955-60 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Little, Henry, 1955-61 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Little, Herbert - Liu, Nien Lung, 1956-63 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Liu, Phyllis (Yung-Ho), 1955-61 (Box 19, Folder 246)
  - Liu, R. - Liu, Yuen, 1960-62 (Box 19, Folder 246)
  - Liu, Yung-Chuang, 1958-60 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Liu, Yu-wan - Lloyd, Mrs. Lewis, 1958-59 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Lo - Lowe, Keith, 1956-61 (Box 19, Folder 248)
  - Lowney - Lu, David, 1962-63 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Lu, Kun-hsi; Lu, Shih-peng, 1952-59, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Luce, Henry W., Chair of Philosophy and Religion (Tunghai University, Taiwan), 1963-69 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - Luce Foundation, The Henry, 1955-67 (Box 19, Folder 251-252)
  - Luce Foundation, The Henry, 1967-71 (Box 20, Folder 253)
  - Luce Foundation Grant for Libraries, 1956-68 (Box 20, Folder 254)
  - Lui - Lyman, 1958-64 (Box 20, Folder 255)
  - Ma, John T., 1955-58 (Box 20, Folder 256)
  - Ma, K. - McCutchen, 1956-64 (Box 20, Folder 256)
  - McD - McKe, 1958-64 (Box 20, Folder 257)
  - McKinney, William A. Roberta, 1955-61 (Box 20, Folder 258)
  - McLean - McNeely, 1960-62 (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - Main, Feng-hwa, 1956-60 (Box 21, Folder 260)
  - Mahoning National Bank, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 260)
  - Magdamo, Priscilla, 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 260)
  - Malayan Christian Council (Board of Missions of the Methodist Church), 1957-61 (Box 21, Folder 261)
  - Malaysia, Methodist schools, 1961, 1964-70 (Box 21, Folder 262-265)
  - Mali - Maquiso, 1958-66 (Box 21, Folder 266)
  - Malone, Carroll B., 1955-59 (Box 21, Folder 266)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 267)
  - Manwell, Judith, 1956-59 (Box 21, Folder 267)
  - Mar, Timothy T. - Marsh, Susan Han, 1952-59 (Box 21, Folder 268)
  - Martin B. - Martin, Edward, 1957-60 (Box 21, Folder 269)
  - Martin, Elizabeth B. (Mrs. Frank, Sr.), 1961-64 (Box 21, Folder 269)
  - Martin, Paul, Estate; Mathes, Frank Alfred, 1956, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 270)
  - Matthias, Virginia Park, 1959-61 (Box 21, Folder 271)
  - Mattox - May, George W., 1959-63 (Box 22, Folder 272)
  - Maynard - Maynor, 1960-64 (Box 22, Folder 272)
  - Medical Schools in China, Data (Cheeloo University, Lingnan University, St. John's University, West China Union University), 1925-26,1940-41,1954 (Box 22, Folder 273)
  - Mei, Y. C. - Melegrito, G. G., 1958-63 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - Mendiola, Luthgarda, 1958-61 (Box 22, Folder 275)
  - Meng, Ching-hung, 1955-63 (Box 22, Folder 276)
  - Merwin, Wallace C., 1958-60, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 277)
  - Meston Training College - Meusner, E. W., 1952-60 (Box 22, Folder 278)
  - Midwest Chinese Student and Alumni Services, 1958-60 (Box 22, Folder 279)
  - Mignon, Charles W., 1959-60 (Box 22, Folder 280)
  - Miller - Mills, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 281)
  - Milne, Muriel (Mrs. Alan H.), 1959-61 (Box 22, Folder 281)
  - Ministry of Education, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 281)
  - Mission Boards: General: Capital Requests, 1959-64 (Box 22, Folder 282)
  - Mission Boards: General: Building Grants and Maintenance, 1960-61 Jan (Box 22, Folder 283)
  - Mission Boards: General: Comparative Giving Representation, 1963-68 (Box 22, Folder 284)
  - Mission Boards: General: Charts, 1964-70 (Box 22, Folder 285)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: American Baptist - Evangelical United, 1958-71 (Box 22, Folder 286)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: Lutheran - Methodist, 1965-72 (Box 22, Folder 287)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: Oberlin-Shansi Memorial Association - Presbyterian Church in Canada, 1965-72 (Box 22, Folder 288)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: Presbyterian: United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1965-72 (Box 22, Folder 289)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: Reformed Church in America, 1965-72 (Box 22, Folder 290)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: United Church of Canada, 1965-71 (Box 22, Folder 290)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: United Church of Christ, Board for World Ministries Council for Church and Ministry, 1965-72 (Box 22, Folder 291)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: Yale-in-China, 1965-71 (Box 22, Folder 291)
  - Mission Boards: Correspondence: Miscellaneous Representatives, 1965-70 (Box 22, Folder 292)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Anglican (English) of Canada, 1964-66 (Box 23, Folder 293)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Anglican Church of Korea, 1967-69 (Box 23, Folder 293)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Baptist: American Baptist Foreign Mission Society and Woman's American Baptist Foreign Mission Society, 1958-71 (Box 23, Folder 294-296)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: British Missionary Societies, 1958-60 (Box 23, Folder 297)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Congregational: American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions after 1961 Jul see: United Church Board for World Ministries, 1958-61 (Box 23, Folder 298-300)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Disciples of Christ: United Missionary Society, 1958-64 (Box 23, Folder 301-302)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Episcopal: Executive Council, 1964-74 (Box 23, Folder 303)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Episcopal: National Council Overseas Department, 1958-61 Jun (Box 23, Folder 304)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Episcopal: National Council Overseas Department, 1961 Jul-1964 (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Evangelical and Reformed: Board of International Missions; after 1961 Jul see: United Church Board for World Ministries, 1958-61 Jun (Box 24, Folder 306)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Evangelical United Brethren Church: Board of Missions, 1958-64 Jun (Box 24, Folder 307-309)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Lutheran, American Lutheran Church: Division of World Missions for earlier correspondence see: Evangelical Lutheran Church: Board of Foreign Missions, 1961-64 (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Lutheran, Evangelical Lutheran Church: Board of Foreign Missions, 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Lutheran, Lutheran Church in America: Board of World Missions, 1961-72 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Lutheran, United Lutheran Church of America: Board of Foreign Missions, 1955-61 (Box 24, Folder 313)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Methodist: Board of Missions see also: Jones, Tracey K., 1958-61 (Box 24, Folder 314-317)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Methodist: Board of Mission, 1962-74 (Box 25, Folder 318-327)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Methodist: Woman's Division of Christian Service, 1958-61 (Box 25, Folder 328-329)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Methodist: Woman's Division of Christian Service, 1962-64 (Box 26, Folder 330-331)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian: Australian Presbyterian Mission, 1964-69 (Box 26, Folder 332)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian: Canada, Presbyterian Church in, 1958-73 (Box 26, Folder 332-334)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian: Presbyterian Church in the U.S. (South), 1958-73 (Box 26, Folder 335-338)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian, Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. (North): Commission on Ecumenical Mission and Relations (C.O.E.M.A.R.), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 339)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian, United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: C.O.E.M.A.R., 1959-60 (Box 26, Folder 340-342)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian, United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: C.O.E.M.A.R., 1961-67 (Box 27, Folder 343-346)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian, United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: C.O.E.M.A.R. - Finance, 1964-74 (Box 27, Folder 347-353)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian, United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: C.O.E.M.A.R. - Fifty Million Fund, 1965-73 (Box 28, Folder 354-356)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Presbyterian, United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: C.O.E.M.A.R. - Representation to U.B.C.H.E.A., 1970-75 (Box 28, Folder 357)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: Reformed Church in America: Board of World Missions, 1958-64 (Box 28, Folder 358-359)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: United Church Board for World Ministries, 1961-64 (Box 28, Folder 360-361)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: United Church of Canada: Board for Overseas Missions as of 1962 Jun - Board of World Mission, 1961-67 Jun (Box 28, Folder 362-367)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: United Church of Canada: Board of World Mission 1967 Ju1-, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 368)
  - Mission Boards: Individual: United Church of Canada: Woman's Missionary Society, 1958-62 (Box 29, Folder 369-370)
  - Missionary Education Publications - Moomaw, Ira G., 1958-64 (Box 29, Folder 371)
  - Moore, A. B., 1960-61 (Box 29, Folder 372)
  - Moore, Arthur J., 1959-60 (Box 29, Folder 372)
  - Moore, Elisabeth Luce (Mrs. Maurice), 1958-71 (Box 29, Folder 373-380)
  - Moore, Robert A. - Morgan, Carrel B. and Dorothy (Loren S. Morgan Memorial Fund), 1955-63 (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - Morgan, Julia, Estate, 1945-49 (Box 29, Folder 382)
  - Morgan, S. - Moyer, Raymond T., 1958-64 (Box 29, Folder 383)
  - Muilenburg - Murray, 1959-63 (Box 30, Folder 384)
  - Na - Nance, 1958-62 (Box 30, Folder 385)
  - Nanking Theological Seminary - Nanking University, 1961-64 (Box 30, Folder 386)
  - Napitupulu, Washington P., 1958-62 (Box 30, Folder 387-388)
  - National Christian Council of Korea National Conference of Architectural Registration Boards, 1959-60 (Box 30, Folder 389)
  - National Council of Churches, 1961-69 (Box 30, Folder 390)
  - New York County Clerk; New York State, Education Department; Board of Regents, 1955-6 (Box 30, Folder 391)
  - New York State, Education Department; Correspondence, 1949-55 (Box 30, Folder 392)
  - New York State, Education Department: Financial Records, 1949-50 (Box 30, Folder 393)
  - New, Yun Tsung Zee, 1958-60 (Box 30, Folder 394)
  - Newcomer, James, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 395)
  - Nikijuluw - Ninde, Frederick Ward, 1955-61 (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1959-60 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - Nommensen University - North Borneo, 1956-64 (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - North, Eric M., 1958-60 (Box 30, Folder 399)
  - North Korea - Nygreen, Glen, 1958-64 (Box 30, Folder 400)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association (see also: Tunghai), 1958-60 (Box 30, Folder 401-403)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association, 1961-64 (Box 31, Folder 404-406)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association: Carlson, Ellsworth C., 1961-63 (Box 31, Folder 407)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association: Faculty Fellowships, 1959-62 (Box 31, Folder 408)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association: Newsletters, 1961-63 (Box 31, Folder 409)
  - Occena, Mateo, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 410)
  - Oh, Ki Hyoung, 1960-61 (Box 31, Folder 410)
  - Olmsted, Robert C., 1959-63 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - Ormisten, J. D., 1962 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - Orndorff, Harriet (Mrs. John), 1960-63 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - Osborn, Ruby M., 1962-64 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - Overholt, William W., 1959 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - Overing Street Mortgage, 1961-62 (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - Owen, George E., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - Pace, Frank Jr., 1959-64 (Box 31, Folder 414)
  - Paik, George L., 1956 (Box 31, Folder 415)
  - Paik, George L. (see also: Yonsei), 1961-64 (Box 31, Folder 415)
  - Palmer, Henry C. T., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Pamp, Frederic E., 1958-63 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Pan, Loretta (Ren-tsin), 1959-60 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Paralejas, Rustico, 1958-60 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Park, Ki-Soon, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 418)
  - Paton, Thomas James, 1959-61 (Box 31, Folder 418)
  - Pei, I. M. - Peng, Jessie, 1961-64 (Box 31, Folder 419)
  - P.E.O. Sisterhood International Peace Scholarships, 1960-61 (Box 31, Folder 420)
  - Perry, Charles, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 420)
  - Petition for Consolidation, 1945, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 421)
  - Petrusz, Gustav W., 1965-70 (Box 31, Folder 422-425)
  - Philippine Claims; Philippine Federation of Christian Churches; Philippine-Wesleyan College, 1958-61 (Box 32, Folder 426)
  - Philippines: Association of Christian Schools and Colleges, 1958-7 (Box 32, Folder 427-430)
  - Philippines: Association of Christian Schools and Colleges, Philippine Christian Colleges, 1956-61 (Box 32, Folder 431-434)
  - Philippines: Association of Christian Schools and Colleges, Printed material, 1964-74 (Box 32, Folder 435)
  - Phillips, C. L., 1960 (Box 32, Folder 436)
  - Phillips Foundation, Ellis L., 1959-62 (Box 32, Folder 436)
  - Pickens, Claude L. Jr. - Prall, George, 1958-64 (Box 32, Folder 437)
  - Presbyterian Junior Year Abroaders, 1959-61 (Box 32, Folder 438)
  - Presidents' Conference, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 439)
  - Presidents' Conference (see also: Librarians' Conference), 1959 (Box 32, Folder 440)
  - Presidents' Conference, 1961-70, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 441-446)
  - Price, Frank W., 1961-64 (Box 33, Folder 447)
  - Price, Harry B., 1964 (Box 33, Folder 447)
  - Price, N. W., 1964 (Box 33, Folder 447)
  - Price, Ruth (Mrs. Walter), 1955-59 (Box 33, Folder 448)
  - Price Waterhouse Co., Audit, 1960-71 (Box 33, Folder 449-450)
  - Priest, Elsie M. (see also: College Files - Tunghai), 1960-69 (Box 34, Folder 451-452)
  - Princeton-in-Asia (see: Series VI) (see: Brumbaugh, T. T. (1965 Feb 24))
  - Pu - Pus, 1961-69 (Box 34, Folder 453)
  - Quillian - Quimby, 1958-60 (Box 34, Folder 454)
  - Raines, Richard C. - Ranson, Charles W., 1959-61 (Box 34, Folder 455)
  - Raterta, Pedro M., 1958-61 (Box 34, Folder 456)
  - Ratliff, Bill and Lynn, 1959-61 (Box 34, Folder 457)
  - Reader's Digest Foundation, 1958-63 (Box 34, Folder 458)
  - Reames, Mark E. Jr., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 459)
  - Reid, W. W., 1959 (Box 34, Folder 459)
  - Reischauer, Edwin O. - Reynolds, Hubert, 1959-65 (Box 34, Folder 460)
  - Rice, Roberta G. - Richelsen, Mark and Elizabeth, 1959-64 (Box 34, Folder 461)
  - Riverside Church, 1958-70 (Box 34, Folder 462)
  - Roberts, W. - Robison, J. T., 1960 (Box 34, Folder 463)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (John D. Rockefeller III), 1958-60 (Box 34, Folder 464)
  - Rood, Wayne - Rubendahl, Howard, 1959-61 (Box 34, Folder 465)
  - Ruei, K. H. - Rugh, Sarah, 1959-61 (Box 34, Folder 466)
  - Ruland Benjamin, Earl Calhoun, 1959-61 (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - Sailer, Randolph C., 1959 (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - St. Mark's Church, Brooklyn, 1959-61 (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - St. Paul's University, Tokyo, Japan, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - Sandelmann, John C., 1958-59 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - Sanders, Albert and Edna - Scott, Annie V., 1957-64 (Box 34, Folder 470)
  - Scott, Ewing C. - Scovel, Frederic G., 1958-61 (Box 34, Folder 471)
  - Seaman, Henry B. and Vera, 1964-68 (Box 34, Folder 472)
  - Sears, Minnie (Mrs. Charles H.), 1956-64 (Box 34, Folder 472)
  - Seely, Albert L., 1962-68 (Box 35, Folder 473-475)
  - Selby, Howard W., 1960 (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Sentman, J. Richard, 1958-59 (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Seoul (Presbyterian) Women's College, 1959-60 (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Shadick, Harold - Shanley, Frank A. (Anna), 1959-61 (Box 35, Folder 477)
  - Sharbough, John W., 1959-64 (Box 35, Folder 478)
  - Shaw, Charles; Shaw, Glenn, 1958-62 (Box 35, Folder 479)
  - Shen, D. - Shen, Y., 1959-64 (Box 35, Folder 479)
  - Sheng, Luke, 1958-59 (Box 35, Folder 479)
  - Shepherd, Ivor N., 1963 (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Sherrill, Henry Knox, 1961-62 (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Shields, Ran T. Fund, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - Shih, Chung Wen, 1955-61 (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - Shih, Peter Y. F., 1957-61 (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - Shipps, Elizabeth, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Shipps, Hammell Flora, 1960-61 (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Shu, Frank, 1961-64 (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Shu, Frank, Scholarship, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Sie, Georgiana (Mrs. Ping-teh), 1961-64 (Box 35, Folder 484)
  - Silliman Memorial Church, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 484)
  - Simandjuntak, I. P., 1958-59 (Box 35, Folder 485)
  - Simkin, Margaret T. - Smiley, Dean F., 1959-63 (Box 35, Folder 486)
  - Smith College - Smith, Eugene L., 1958-61 (Box 35, Folder 487)
  - Smith, Frances Grace. Bequest, 1949-60 (Box 35, Folder 488)
  - Smith, Frances Grace, Bequest, 1960-61 (Box 36, Folder 489)
  - Smith, Frances Grace, Bequest, Letters re: Litigation, 1960-64 (Box 36, Folder 490)
  - Smith, Gordon F., 1958-61 (Box 36, Folder 491)
  - Smith, John C., 1958-59 (Box 36, Folder 491)
  - Smith, Maida Morton (Morton-Smith), 1949,1951,1960-61 (Box 36, Folder 492)
  - Smith, Otto M., 1958-59 (Box 36, Folder 492)
  - Smith, Paul X., Co., 1959-60 (Box 36, Folder 492)
  - Smith, Robert Wayne, 1958-59 (Box 36, Folder 493)
  - Smythe, Lewis S. C., 1957-60 (Box 36, Folder 494)
  - Snider, Girvin N., 1959-60, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 495)
  - Sockman, Ralph W. - Soo, Thoewin, 1959-62 (Box 36, Folder 496)
  - Sovik, Arne, 1961-65, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 497)
  - Sovik, Edward, 1963-64 (Box 36, Folder 497)
  - Speer, Emma Margaret, 1959-61 (Box 36, Folder 497)
  - Speidel, William Eleana, 1957-64 (Box 36, Folder 498)
  - Spicer, Eva D. - Sprague, Lloyd Drummond, 1958-63 (Box 36, Folder 499)
  - Starr Co., Inc., C. V. (Starr Foundation), 1958-61,64 (Box 36, Folder 500)
  - Stevenson, Theodore, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 501)
  - Stillman Foundation, Inc., Leland, 1957-63 (Box 36, Folder 501)
  - Stowe, David M., 1964 (Box 36, Folder 502)
  - Stowe, Everett M., 1959 (Box 36, Folder 502)
  - Strauss, Frederick G. - Strawbridge, G., 1957-61 (Box 36, Folder 502-505)
  - Stuart, John Leighton, 1959-63 (Box 37, Folder 506)
  - Student Center, Singapore, 1955-61 (Box 37, Folder 507)
  - Studley, Ellen M., 1958-64 (Box 37, Folder 508)
  - Subanu, Surate (also Soebanoe), 1958-61 (Box 37, Folder 509)
  - Suh, Doo Soo, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 510)
  - Sun Life Assurance Co., 1958-73 (Box 37, Folder 511-513)
  - Sun, Mona, 1958-60 (Box 37, Folder 514)
  - Sutton, Willard J. of Christian Colleges in Asia (see: New File Addendum - Appraisal of the Protestant Christian Effort in Higher Education in Asia(), 1960
  - Sword, William H., 1960-62 (Box 37, Folder 515)
  - Syracuse-in-Asia, 1958-68 (Box 37, Folder 515-517)
  - Taft, Eleanor (Mrs. Charles P.), 1958-59 (Box 38, Folder 518)
  - Tainan Theological College (see also: Series IV), 1962-64 (Box 38, Folder 518)
  - Taiwan Tribes Church, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 519)
  - Tan, Cheng-chiang, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 519)
  - Tang, Chen-chi (Charles), 1956-59 (Box 38, Folder 519)
  - Tang, Yi-Noo, 1959-60 (Box 38, Folder 520)
  - T'ao, Betty, 1954-55 (Box 38, Folder 520)
  - Tapping, T. Hawley, 1957-62 (Box 38, Folder 521-524)
  - Taylor, Arthur, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 525)
  - Taylor, Norman W., 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 525)
  - Taylor, P. - Taylor W., 1960-64 (Box 38, Folder 526)